ghcf.org 2013-09-24

# 

                                             Internet Privacy Policy
Greater Houston Community Foundation respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Internet Sites
("Sites"), and has created this privacy statement to explain what information we gather from your visit to
our Sites, and how such information may be used.
Use of Information: As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or
e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to Greater Houston Community Foundation sites.
However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Greater Houston
Community Foundation's Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating
system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience.
Security: Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no
data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect
your personal information, Greater Houston Community Foundation cannot ensure or warrant the security of
any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we
make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Use of IP Addresses: An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet
provider whenever you're surfing the Web. When you requests pages from Greater Houston Community
Foundation Sites, our servers log your IP address. Greater Houston Community Foundation collects IP addresses
for the purposes of system administration and to audit the use of our Site. We do not link IP addresses to
anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you are anonymous to us.
We may use your IP addresses in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if we feel it is
necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use or to protect our service, Sites, customers, or others.
Links to Other Sites: Greater Houston Community Foundation is not responsible for the content or practices of
third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may also be linked to websites operated by other
companies. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site's respective privacy policies and practices.
Contact Us: If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our Sites, or your dealings
with our Sites, you can contact:
Greater Houston Community Foundation, 5120 Woodway Drive, Suite 6000, Houston, TX 77056.
Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to Greater Houston Community Foundation such as
your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never
shared with third parties.
                 To view educational material on consumer privacy, please see http://www.ftc.gov/ .
Your Acceptance of These Terms: By using Greater Houston Community Foundation's Sites, you signify your
acceptance of the Greater Houston Community Foundation Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this
policy, please do not use our Sites. Greater Houston Community Foundation reserves the right to modify, alter
or otherwise update this policy at any time, so visitors are encouraged to review this policy from time to time.
Your continued use of the Greater Houston Community Foundation Sites following the posting of changes to
these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Last updated October, 2011
